SQLite的高效查询能力，使得数据行的删除
Using SQLite makes it easy to delete,
update, and
更新和插入更加容易
insert rows,
using highly expressive queries.
甚至当你修改数据库的时候还能插入新的列
One can even add new columns
as you revision your database,
并保留现有的用户数据
while retaining existing user data.
几乎所有流行的Android应用
It's not a surprise that
just about every popular app
都或多或少使用了SQLite，这并不惊奇
makes some use of SQLite in Android.
这是Android 解决方案中重要而有力的组成部分
It's a very powerful and important
component of the Android solution.
Android 还提供了大量的帮助函数，使得使用数据库更加
Android also provides a huge set of
helper functions to make working with
方便，包括数据库的自动查询和建立
databases easy, including functions
to automate query building,
支持ListView显示的查询甚至是编译语句
display list views, and
even utilize pre-compiled statements.
如果想了解更多有关Android 数据库的知识，可以查看用户手册
For more information about databases
in Android, see the instructor notes.
这就是当你开始在Android上做数据存储时所需要了解的
Well that's what you need to know to get
started with data storage on Android.
这一切都被记录在文档中，你可以在
All of this is documented
if you search for
developer.android.com 上查询有关数据存储的知识
data storage on developer.android.com.
我们将会使用这些存储API去构建我们的天气应用的数据库
We'll be working with these storage
APIs to build our sunshine database.